aspcacommunity.ning.com 2007-10-11

# Network Privacy Policy - ASPCA Online Community

### Network Privacy Policy

**←[Back](http://aspcacommunity.ning.com/)**

Updated: October 6, 2007

The Network Creator of this Network (“we”) wants you to understand how we treat your Personal Data. This Network runs on top of the Ning Platform, through which Ning, Inc. (“Ning”) provides various services to Members of the Network. We define your Personal Data as any data from which it is practical to directly determine your identity. We have established this Privacy Policy to explain how your Personal Data is collected this Network, and how your Personal Data is used and disclosed by the Network Creator. Any capitalized term not defined in this Privacy Policy has the meaning which we lay out in the [Network Member Agreement](http://aspcacommunity.ning.com/main/authorization/termsOfService?previousUrl=http%3A%2F%2Faspcacommunity.ning.com%2Fmain%2Fauthorization%2FprivacyPolicy%3FpreviousUrl%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Faspcacommunity.ning.com%252F#network).

**You acknowledge that your Personal Data may be processed by the Network Creator in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be different than the laws in your jurisdiction.**

#### Collection of Information

##### Personally Identifiable Information

Once you register with or join this Network using your Ning ID, you are not anonymous to the Network Creator. From that point forward, Ning will share with the Network Creator your account information and Personal Data related to this Network.

When registering with the Network, you provide at least your email address, a Member-created password, and the answers to the required profile questions, which might be publicly viewable by other Members or limited to just the Network Creator.

This Network may validate the domain from which your email address originates (e.g., gmail.com or hotmail.com).

This Network does not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of 13.

##### Cookies and Passive Data Collection

Ning automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Ning cookie information, and the page you request. As the Network Creator, we might also capture this information.

You should be aware that other websites visited before visiting the Network might place personally identifiable information within the URL of your browser during a visit to that previous website, and the Network would unintentionally collect that information as part of the referring URL information.

##### Content and Use of Networks

When you post Content (or send messages) in this or any Social Network(s) on the Ning Platform that enable direct sharing of information with other Members and visitors, other Members and visitors will have access to any Personal Data in such Content. Such Personal Data (which is publicly posted) is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Because you may voluntarily disclose any Personal Data in these public areas, you should be careful about the information you choose to disclose. The Network Creator does not control that disclosure, and is not liable in any way for anyone's use or misuse of the information in the disclosure. In other words, use caution and judgment here.

#### How this Network Uses Information

##### Personally Identifiable Information

We will send you administrative messages, and email updates regarding your account on the Network. We will also send you broadcast messages. You can opt out of receiving any and all promotional notifications from your “My Settings” page on this Network. 

##### Cookies and Passive Data Collection

The Network uses cookie, IP address, and URL information to improve the Network. Cookies may be used to save your Ning ID and session validators on your hard drive, and may use them to provide tailored services to you, as they become available. 

#### Disclosures

##### To Ning

We will disclose your Personal Data that we collect to Ning, which Ning is required to treat in accordance with the [Ning Privacy Policy](http://www.ning.com/about/privacy.html).

##### Law Enforcement

The Network Creator may disclose Personal Data if required by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order, where required by law, or, at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to protect the safety of any individual or the general public or to prevent violation of our Member Agreement or the rights of the Network Creator or any third party.

##### Ning Affiliates

If we share may share some of all of your Personal Data with our corporate affiliates, we will seek to require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

#### Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of your Personal Data, including email addresses, to a that entity. We will notify you (via a posting on this Network or email (in our discretion) of such a transfer, and you may choose to modify their registration information at that time. This means if you are concerned about your Personal Data migrating to a new owner, you can deactivate your account. 

#### Security

Since the Network runs on the Ning Platform, we rely on the security procedures in place on the Ning Platform. Please see the [Ning Privacy Policy](http://www.ning.com/about/privacy.html) for details. 

#### Updating or Removing Member Information

You may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information you have submitted to us, by going to your Network account. You may remove your Member information from our Network by deactivating your Network account. Even if you update or remove your information from the Network, however, your Personal Data may be retained in our backup files and archives. 

You can decline to share Personal Data with us by not registering on this Network. 

#### International Members

By visiting the Network and providing your Personal Data, you acknowledge and agree that, due to the international dimension of the Network, we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in the United States where laws protecting Personal Data may be different from the laws in your jurisdiction. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

#### Revisions to This Policy

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy in accordance with the “Amendments” section of our Network Member Agreement. 

#### Contacting the Network Creator

Members with questions about this Privacy Policy may contact the Network Creator by sending them a message on the Network. 

#### Feedback

We welcome your feedback on this document.
